Hello Hello friends Welcome to my YouTube
channel C Today Update Ajib friends if you are new to the channel
then subscribe to the channel and
press the bell icon to stay notified
Uncle friends today a very big news is coming out from such side on
which
all VLEs should pay attention in which
friends I am going to tell you
what is new coming out friends right now
news is coming out that the
payment of PMG Disha will be folded the main reason of this is that
friends friends
fake news is being spread by some people on social media and WhatsApp that
₹ 250 percent are being made on email and outcome from one side friends those people who have done
such work through the
script or software of packed email and outcome the
payment of all those people will be folded
and friends those who are making such messages viral on social media
CSC is going to take strict action against all those people and
legal action is going to be taken against them
so this was the biggest news of today that
PMG will be given that the payment of those people who were supposed to get the
payment will not come now those who have sent
an email and outcome who have done this
Please, those who did not use the software,
their payment will come easily but
those who got the work done through this software and script or got the
work done from someone else for fifty paise or one rupee, their
payment will also be folded by C
and their payment will never be
released in future, such and such has said so
friends, that's all in today's video and keep doing the work
you are doing
and do subscribe to our channel so
that you get to learn new information, do it
[Music]